One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward! Hands up!!
"I'm almost there, just a little further and I'll have the answer."
That's what I believed as I sailed into this new world.
That's right, the pieces of our dreams are joined together as one.
We're connected by unwavering bonds, let's head for a bright future!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Always look up!
Keep your head held high!
Always step up!
Fly over the waves!
Our dreams have been carefully joined together.
Now let's head for the future!
We drift forward, riding the waves,
meeting people and saying goodbye, then doing it again,
all under this flag...
Pain I don't want to forget is kept in my heart.
There was a day when I softly carved it there.
I won't let anyone take my freedom.
I grasp it tightly in my hands!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Always look up!
Keep your head held high!
Always step up!
Fly over the waves!
Our dreams have been carefully joined together.
Now let's head for the future!
The Alliance's Target and the Departure!
Listen up, you damn pirates!
You pirates can have the tanker!
And this is the line between good and evil!
Don't you dare cross this line!
You get that, Straw Hat Pirates?!
That's right!
Who told you to do something so ridiculous?
All I said was to not get too friendly with the pirates.
If we're gonna do it, then we should do it properly,
Vice-Admiral Smo.
But the line doesn't count for medical teams.
I already made contact with the G-5 base.
We wait here until a ship comes to pick us up.
Yes, sir!
Really?! You're giving yourself up, Brownbeard?
We just became friends!
Apparently, the experiments that were performed on us
were a little poisonous.
We'll be treated if we turn ourselves in.
I get it now.
Hey hey, Straw Hat!
I just told you not to cross the line!
Were you even listening to me?!
Like I care!
That's something you guys just made up!
Besides, prison will be an improvement
after having Caesar use me as a guinea pig.
And I don't have a crew anymore.
It felt really good to see you send Caesar flying.
Thanks a lot.
Heave, ho!
Alright, keep pulling.
You should have told me earlier
that we were gonna take this tanker.
I would've fought somewhere else if I knew I'd have to fix it.
There we go!
What's the ruckus?
What's going on?
Luffy!
P-Please stop him!
H-H-He's a murderer!
Murderer?!
Who's a murderer?
It's Law!
Traf?
What's going on over there?
I killed someone too!
No, Kin'emon-san was already dead...
but I broke him!
Not only is he dead, now he's broken!
He's dead smashed!
W-W-What do we do now?!
Will he be alright if we glue him back together?!
As if that would work, you idiot!
Momonosuke!
Why are you still alive?!
Why did you do that, Sanji-san?!
He freaked me out!
You were the one shouting about him being dead
when he's perfectly fine!
Hey, take a look at that.
Someone who was
supposed to be killed by the gas is still alive.
Isn't it great, Kin'emon-san? I had thought...
Father!
Mo-Momonosuke?
Momonosuke!
I'm so glad that you are alive!
F-Father!
Momonosuke?
Now that I think about it,
he did say that he was originally human.
My son, you are stark naked.
Transform!
Child of the Wano Country (Son of Kin'emon) Momonosuke
I would expect no less from a child of the Wano Country.
You look good in a kimono.
But father, how did you find...
Momonosuke!
Law!
Get out here, Law!
You...
Just what were you doing to the children?!
If anything has happened to them then I...
That's why I told you not to look. I was just...
slicing up their bodies.
They've been fed narcotics. Their recovery
will be long and hard, there's no way around that.
Oh, Raccoon Dog-chan!
Raccoon Dog-kun!
A-Are you all okay?
That guy with the fluffy head...
just took all the bad stuff out of our bodies.
Huh?
It was scary, but I feel much better now!
It was fun having our bodies in pieces.
Now I'm hungry.
I see.
But Mocha hasn't woken up yet.
Mocha was fighting to help us, right?
I didn't know that Master was such a bad guy.
It's a bit fuzzy, but I remember
Mocha coughing up blood and collapsing!
Hey, Raccoon Dog-kun.
Uh, I'm a reindeer.
Mocha's gonna be okay, isn't she?
We're gonna go home together, right Raccoon Dog-kun?
Of course.
You're getting out of this nightmare.
Where's the orange-haired lady?
She's the one that's going to take us home, right?
We want to thank her!
Let's save these children!
How am I supposed to turn my back...
On children who are crying for help?!
Hello.
From now on, the Navy will take care of you.
No way!
What about the robot?
What about the rubber-man?
What about the guy with the curly eyebrows?
That smells great!
I wonder what Sanji's making.
I can't wait.
Nami?
Have you worked things out with the Navy?
Yeah.
I'm going to leave everything to the Navy.
I may have told them that I'd save them...
but we're pirates
and that would probably make things difficult.
Yeah, we'd probably wind up
being blamed for their abductions.
It's best to leave them
with people on the justice side of the line.
You're right.
Also...
I am begging you...
Allow me to take care of the children!
I just have a weakness for the eyes of a female marine.
Female marines?
Yeah.
They're reassuring to me.
Oh yeah, your mom was a marine, wasn't she?
It's always best to be saved by a strong, kind-hearted female marine.
I think so too.
I don't want to hear that from you.
Well, you're the one that said it!
Newkama Kenpo Secret Technique, 99th Vital Recipe!
Let's revive your cold and tired bodies!
Hormone Soup with Sea Pig!
If you haven't eaten for several days...
then take your time and savor the meal,
starting with the soup.
It looks so good!
You're really hungry, right?
Momo, Sanji's food is the best.
I have no need for it!
I am not hungry in the slightest!
Hey, wait you brat!
What are you gonna do with that dish?!
I won't forgive anyone that wastes food,
even if they're a kid!
I shall eat.
H-Hey.
Delicious!
What is this?
I feel stronger!
What delicious food!
Delicious.
Father...!
Let us accept their food.
The truth is that they saved my life.
You may trust these people.
You've had nothing to eat until now, right?
You have done well to endure.
It must have been hard.
It's alright now.
Let us believe that the others have endured as well.
Now, we shall continue to live, Momonosuke!
Yeah.
What happened?
Is it so delicious that it makes you cry?
No you idiot, they've clearly been through a lot.
Just what happened to these guys?
Hmm?
What happened to
the line between good and evil, you jerks?!
It's a truce, bro.
Okay then, why don't you guys
go get some booze from the tanker?
With pleasure.
Some juice as well!
Hey, Straw Hatter.
We need to leave this place quickly.
If we stay and eat, new enemies will arrive.
Really?
Tell everyone else.
Right, got it.
Let's party!
Cheers!
Father...
A warrior shouldn't let anyone see their tears.
What's that supposed to be, Luffy?
Cheers, bro.
Yeah!
Wait for it...
One, two, three!
Here you go.
Thank you.
Mocha!
Vice-Admiral Smokey!
We're gonna go back inside.
What's wrong?
We made Caesar spill the weakness of the poison gas.
Our comrades are still alive and we can still save them!
Why are you still alive, Smoker?
Law...
There's no way that you would believe
that I'd keep a promise to a pirate like you.
But if you really wanted to silence me,
then you had plenty of chances to kill me.
What are you planning on using Straw Hat to do?
Use?
Who's the one being used?
Which of the Four Emperors are you talking about?
The target is...
Kaidou of the Beasts.
As long as the first one isn't Shanks, I'm fine with it.
Because I plan on defeating all of them!
You want to defeat all of them?!
While that may coincide with our goals,
you're underestimating them too much.
They are the emperors of this sea,
and battled Whitebeard himself for their turf.
Among them, Kaidou of the Beasts
is known as the most powerful creature in the world.
What?! He's not even human?
The purpose of our alliance is to take down Kaidou.
The probability of our plan succeeding is...
Well, it's best to assume it's extremely low.
What, really?!
We shouldn't accept his offer, Luffy.
I see.
Alright, let's do it.
Hold on, now!
There was no real reason why I let you live, White Hunter.
By the way, I plan on heading to Green Bit.
I wonder if the Straw Hat Crew is too much for me to handle?
Rubber...
Gluttony!
You're amazing!
He stretches!
Cool!
We're G-5.
Even crying kids shut up when they see us!
I thought you guys were gonna use the tanker?
Nah, that isn't what we were doing.
Nami and Chopper said that they refuse to set sail
until they've made sure the kids are off safely.
And I can't be bothered to wait for
another Navy ship to come here,
so use that to take the kids.
Get on the ship, kids!
We're taking you home!
Hey, hey, Straw Hats!
If the tanker is ours then...
this is the new line!
Don't even think of crossing it.
This is the line between good and evil.
Understand? Don't come any closer!
Again?
Weren't we just partying together?
Don't be an idiot!
In regards to that, we are really grateful for the food.
But, you guys are pirates!
A shame on all humanity!
Heave, ho!
What's this?
Big sis Nami?
Chopper-chan?
Where's the robot?
Huh? Where'd all the pirate guys go?
Get out of the way, you guys. You're being annoying.
It's a barrier!
Don't look at the pirates!
You guys are pretty much pirates yourselves, G-5.
But, it looks like they're all safely on board.
We are justice!
We kill all pirates who endanger civilians!
Pirates are the scum of the world!
We are justice!
Don't let the kids lay eyes on them!
Run, you guys!
If you don't want to die then start running!
They said that Vegapunk is gonna help them
with the candy problem.
Really?!
That's reassuring.
Swirly guy!
You're in the way, Navy!
Please move!
Any of you who want to say goodbye to a pirate is a bad kid!
Anyone who says thanks will be
thrown off the boat and left on the island!
Listen up!
Pirates are evil and the Navy is good!
Pirates are unforgivable!
We stand against all pirates!
But they said they would save us...
and they did!
Even though they knew nothing about us...
We're so big and would only get in their way, but they took us with them anyway!
I want to go home.
We'll go back soon.
Just a bit longer.
Even though this is an deserted island
that no one ever comes to...
They came for us!
I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry... that we didn't find you sooner!
Pirates are dirty and rotten!
But the Navy...
If you won't even let us say thank you
when we leave...
then the Navy can just...
Wait! I'm sorry!
Say no to pirates!
Say yes to the Navy!
And even more than that!
The Navy is righteous and brave and-
Stop this at once!
How disgraceful!
B-But Tashigi-chan, if we don't keep insulting them...
We'll end up...
actually liking these outlaws!
E-Even though they're pirates!
What weird marines!
Hey everyone!
Thanks for saving us!
When we grow up we're definitely...
gonna become pirates!
No you won't!
Well then, let's get going.
Hey, is that guy coming with us?
Oh yeah, we haven't told you about the alliance.
Straw Hat, prepare yourself!
Next time we meet, we'll be enemies!
See you later!
We'll definitely catch you!
You brats seem to have the devil's luck.
To think that the sky path would end here.
Young master!
Damn it!
That bastard Law really did betray us!
I'm sorry -dasuyan.
I wanna apologize with my death.
I was needed and I couldn't help!
Isn't this the life boat from our tanker?
I'm so ashamed -dasuyan.
We did everything we could.
It's alright. No need to say anything.
You were just following my orders.
Now this is surprising.
I didn't think that the boss would come out himself.
Is that you, Law? Long time, no see.
Couldn't you have stayed so we could meet in person?
If you're searching for Caesar, then he's with me.
J-Joker, please save me!
Where are Baby 5 and Buffalo's bodies?
Who knows.
That isn't what we're talking about.
Let's make a deal.
Hey Law, don't try to be so tough.
A brat shouldn't try to act like an adult.
Where are you right now?
You shouldn't anger me.
Anger?
Your most important trading partner is...
one of the Four Emperors.
The great pirate, Kaidou of the Beasts.
You're the one who shouldn't anger him.
What do you think would happen
if he found out you couldn't make Smiles anymore.
He isn't a man you can negotiate with.
There would be a brutal battle.
Young master, your face...
You would be killed.
You're taking this joke too far, Law.
What do I have to do for you to give back Caesar?
What are your demands?
Give up your position as a Warlord.
What an insolent brat!
Then we won't be able to stay on Dressrosa!
Throw away everything you've gained these
past ten years and return to being a normal pirate.
Of course, if you do that
then the Admirals from Navy HQ will hunt you down.
You have until tomorrow's morning news.
If I see that you've retired from the Warlords then I will contact you again.
If there is nothing, then all negotiations are off.
Later.
Hey wait, Law!
Young Master!
Translation & initial syncing, Yibis Fansubs
Timing, Galaxy 9000, , Timing Checking, Sewil
Quality-checking, Sewil, Galaxy 9000, Feeso
Soundtracking, Halee
Video editing, Sewil
Raw provider, OPC Raws (Opening), Crunchyroll (Episode)
Title card artist, misakibyakko.deviantart.com